Guide to the Dorothy Hayden Cudahy Papers AIA.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III. Photographs, 1918-2009; 4 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 3 flat boxes, and 2 manuscript boxes
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parades, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade--Chief Brehon, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Social and Professional Organizations, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Social and Professional Organizations: includes Sports, 1930-1974, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - United Irish Counties Association of New York, 1964, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - United Irish Counties Association--Events, circa 1950s-2000s (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Unspecified Events, 1980s-2000s (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Unspecified Event with Ed Koch, 1980s (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified Events and People, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7, Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Weddings, circa 1930s-1940s, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 69th Regiment New York National Guard Football Team G.A.A., 1935-09-29 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Series IV. Ephemera, 1937-2006; 7 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 4 manuscript boxes, 4 flat file folders, 2 custom boxes, 4 flat boxes, and 1 packing box
  This series consists of greeting cards, newspapers, material objects, and ephemera collected by Dorothy Hayden Cudahy and John J. Cudahy. Material in this series dates from 1937 to 2006 and includes sashes worn by Dorothy at various St. Patrick's Day Parades, plaques commemorating work and achievements of Dorothy and John, and the football from the 1947 Cavan-Kerry All-Ireland Senior Football Championship held at the Polo Grounds in New York City. Indidvidual plaques are listed by the granting organization. This series also contains digital photographs of 39 plaques.
  - American-Irish Legislators Society, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Ancient Order of Hibernians St. Patrick's Day Parade and Celebration Committee, 1989-10-21 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Assemblyman Frederick D. Schmidt, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn Catholic Charities, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Cavan-Kerry football: All-Ireland Finals, Polo Grounds, New York, Sep 14, 1947; Football is located in plexi-glass box in stacks. (Box 40)
  - Cavan-Kerry football: Newspaper clippings about, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - City Council Proclamation, March 14, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Comhaltas Ceoltoiri Eireann-Martin Mulvihill Branch, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - County Clare's P. B. & S. Association, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Department of Traffic badge, undated (Box 39)
  - Events, 1979-2006 (Box 49, Folder 18-21)
  - Grand Marshall Photo Album--photographs and photocopy of album, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 1-4)
  - Greeting Cards I, circa 1940s (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Greeting Cards II, circa 1940s (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Greeting Cards III, circa 1940s (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Greeting Cards IV, circa 1940s (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Greeting Cards V, circa 1940s (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Greeting Cards VI, circa 1940s (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Greeting Cards VII, circa 1940s (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - The Irish World, Aug 1943 (Box 41, Folder 2-3)
  - Irish Echo, Jun 1945 - Aug 1945 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Irish Advocate, Feb 1945 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Irish American Defense Fund, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Ladies Ancient Order of Hibernians, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Mid Hudson St. Patrick's Day Parade, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 3, Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings: various, 1937, 1953-1997, undated; 1953-1997 (Box 5, Folder 27, Box 45, Folder 6, Box 39, Folder 2)
  - New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade--Grand Marshall, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7-11)
  - New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade--Legislative Resolutions, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade--Grand Marshall Outfit, 1989 (Box 56, Box 53)
    The outfit Dorothy Hayden Cudahy wore as Grand Marshall of the New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade consists of a green dress with matching green boots and a cream knit coat with matching pillbox hat. Photographs of Cudahy wearing this outfit can be found in the file titled "New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade--Grand Marshall" in Series III.
  - New York City St. Patrick's Day Parade--Programs, 1977-1988 (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
  - N. Y. Knock Shrine Committee, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Photo Collages, c. 2010 (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Plaques--photographs, undated; cuid34407 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_AIA_1_ER_1)
  - Shamrock Decoration from Danny Devlin's Tuxedo Ballroom, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade Grand Marshall Sashes, 1989 (Box 38, Box 89)
  - Tickets, Badges, 1968-1980 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Traditional Irish Musicians Association, Inc., 1972 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Series V. Commercial Recordings, 1916-1992, undated; 28.5 Linear Feet in 9 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and 19 packing boxes
  Arrangement
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor. The recordings are arranged by format, with the bulk being 33 rpm grooved recordings and the remaining items 78 rpm and 45 rpm grooved recordings. Within these boxes there is some arrangement by artist name, but this is not consistent across the boxes. There are inventories for the 33s and 78s, and the 33s inventory contains location information. Both inventories contain title, artist, publisher, and date information, as well as record company catalog numbers.
  This series consists of over a thousand audio recordings collected by Dorothy Hayden Cudahy and John J. Cudahy for the Irish Memories radio program. The recordings date from 1957 to 1989 and were acquired by the Cudahys directly from the artists or purchased during trips to Ireland. A wide variety of Irish music is featured, including both domestic and international artists, and ranging from sean-nós singing, ceili bands, show bands, and popular songs. Musical groups represented in the collection include The McNulty Family, the Gallowglass Ceili Band, the Tulla Ceili Band, the Clancy Brothers, the Boys of the Lough, the Bothy Band, Clannad, the Chieftains, and the Wolfe Tones. Individual artists include John McCormack, Michael Coleman, Willie Brady, Delia Murphy, Anne Greehy, Michael O'Duffy, Birdie Gallagher, Carmel Quinn, Teres Duffy, Ruby Murray, Frank Patterson, Connie Foley, Mary McGonigle, Dermot O'Brien, Jackie Roche, and Paddy Noonan. Of particular interest are a collection of Comhaltas Ceoltoiri Eireann tours of the United States and Canada, circa 1972 to 1989; two tribute albums to President John F. Kennedy and his address to Dail Eireann; and the albums of various New York Emerald Society Pipe bands.
  - 33 rpm Recordings, 1957-1989; 18.3 Linear Feet in 19 packing boxes and 1 manuscript box
    - Inventory, 1957-1989; 19 Linear Feet (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Recordings, 1957-1989; 19 Linear Feet 19 boxes of 33 rpm records collected by Dorothy Hayden Cudahy and John Cudahy for the Irish Memories Radio Show. (Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15, Box 16, Box 17, Box 18, Box 19, Box 20, Box 21, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24, Box 25, Box 57, Box 58, Box 59, Box 60, Box 61, Box 62, Box 63, Box 64, Box 65, Box 66, Box 67, Box 68, Box 69, Box 70)
  - 78 rpm Recordings, undated; 7 Linear Feet in 6 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
    - Inventory, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Recordings, undated; 6 Linear Feet 6 boxes of 78 rpm records collected by Dorothy Hayden Cudahy and John Cudahy for the Irish Memories Radio Show. (Box 26, Box 27, Box 28, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Box 71, Box 72, Box 73, Box 74, Box 75, Box 76, Box 88, Box 51)
    - Dorothy Hayden Show, Irish Program Theme, "Kilkenny for Me", undated (Box 31)
  - 45 rpm Recordings, 1916-1992; 1958-1988; 7.85 Linear Feet in 13 small LP boxes
    - Side A: McLaughlins, "Gra Mo Chroi" Side B: McLaughlins, "For Baby (For Bobbie)", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 1)
    - Side A: McGonigle, Mary, "Farewell to the Green Hills of Erin" Side B: McGonigle, Mary, "My Hometown in Co. Mayo", 1963 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 2)
    - Side A: Sinton, Aileen Hamilton, "Valentia Island Song" Side B: Sinton, Aileen Hamilton, "Shana Golden", 1969 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 3)
    - Side A: The Dubliners, "Nelson's Farewell" Side B: The Dubliners, "The Foggy Dew", 1966 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 4)
    - Side A: "Galway Shawl" Side B: "Isle of Inis Free", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 5)
    - Side A: Daly, Pat, "Irish Soldier Laddie" Side B: Daly, Pat, "Liverpool Lou", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 6)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Dermot, "The Ballad of Brian Boru" Side B: O'Brien, Dermot, "Medley - King of the Fairies, Madam Bonaparte", 1969 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 7)
    - Side A: Addinell, Roy, "Black Rose" Side B: Addinell, Roy, "My Fair One", 1969 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 8)
    - Side A: Real McCoy, "Quick Joey Small (Run Joey Run)" Side B: Real McCoy, "Happiness is Love", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 9)
    - Side A: Mulhare, Martin, "The Steeplechase and Reevies No. 9" Side B: Mulhare, Martin, "O'Mahony's Fancy and George White's Favorite", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 10)
    - Side A: The Broadsiders, "Grandfather's Will" Side B: The Broadsiders, "Deportees", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 11)
    - Side A: Turkington, Tom, "Swallow's Tail: Green Gates: Reconciliation" and "Silver Spray: Miller's Daughter" Side B: Doris, Malachy, "Marches: Irish Rover: Green Fields; O'Donnel Abu" and "Irish Barn Dance: Phil the Fluter; Keel Row; Ould Rigadoo", 1962 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 12)
    - Side A: Niddy Griddy Band, "Dinny Girgy" Side B: Niddy Griddy Band, "Summertime", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 13)
    - Side A: Cowan, Peter, "When the Snow is On the Roses" Side B: Cowan, Peter, "Lonely Street at Midnight", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 14)
    - Side A: The Alexander Brothers, "Two Little Teardrops" Side B: The Alexander Brothers, "The Flying Scotsmen", 1967 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 15)
    - Side A: The Johnstons, "I Never Will Marry" Side B: The Johnstons, "Banks of Claudy", 1967 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 16)
    - Side A: Brennan, Florrie, "O Huro My Johnny" Side B: Brennan, Florrie, "Red Bloomers", 1969 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 17)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry, "Among the Wicklow Hills" Side B: Cunningham, Larry, "The World You Left Behind", 1966 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 18)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Where is the Summertime?" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "He Walks Like You", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 19)
    - Side A: The Cadets featuring Gregory, "The Dying Ranger" Side B: The Cadets featuring Gregory, "A Storeen Bawn", 1969 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 20)
    - Side A: The Freshmen, "Go Granny Go (The Little Old Lady from Pasadena)" Side B: The Freshmen, "Look at the Sunshine", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 21)
    - Side A: McCauley, Johnny, "Destination Donegal" Side B: McCauley, Johnny, "Cottage on the Borderline", 1966 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 22)
    - Side A: Gallagher, Bridie, "Johnny Gray" Side B: Gallagher, Bridie, "Hillside in Scotland", 1958 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 23)
    - Side A: The Three Coins, "Kitty From Baltimore" Side B: The Three Coins, "Ramblin' Boy", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 24)
    - Side A: Big Johnny, "Biddy Reilly" Side B: Big Johnny, "Tippy Toeing", 1967 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 25)
    - Side A: Doris, Malachy, "Boys of Blue Hill: The Kingston: Harvest Home" and "Irish Waltz: Slieve Gallion Braes: Rose of Mooncoin: Lived Beside the Anner" Side B: Doris, Malachy, "Belfast: Dunphys: Off to California", Turkington, Tom, "Murphy's Hornpipe: Tudor Laddie", 1962 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 26)
    - Side A: Moore, Butch, "Just Call Me Lonesome" Side B: Moore, Butch, "A Good Thing Goin'", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 27)
    - Side A: Max, Pat, "Too Much" Side B: Max, Pat, "Girl From New Orleans", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 28)
    - Side A: Kathleen & Deirdre, "Bridal Path" Side B: Kathleen & Deirdre, "Catch the Bouquet", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 29)
    - Side A: The Tritones, "My Land" Side B: The Tritones, "Love So Soft and Warm", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 30)
    - Side A: O Riada, Sean, "An Tine Bheo" Side B: O Riada, Sean, "An Tine Bheo", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 31)
    - Side A: Maguire, Sean, "Single Reels: Walls of Limerick, Petronella, London Lassies, Devil Among The Tailors" Side B: Maguire, Sean, "Jigs: Idle Road, Kings Favorite", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 32)
    - Side A: Dunphy, Sean, "When The Fields Are White With Daisies" Side B: Dunphy, Sean, "What Am I Doing Hangin' 'Round?", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 33)
    - Side A: Tony & The Graduates, "I Wanna Live" Side B: Tony & The Graduates, "Angel", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 34)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Dermot, "Rosin the Bow" Side B: O'Brien, Dermot, "Walkin' in the Sunshine", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 35)
    - Side A: Gerry & The Ohios, "The Club Kick" Side B: Gerry & The Ohios, "You're the Nearest Thing to Heaven", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 36)
    - Side A: Rice, Bill, "Boys in Blue (A Hero's Death)" Side B: Rice, Bill, "Truck Driving Man", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 37)
    - Side A: Foley, Connie, "Coortin' in the Kitchen" Side B: Foley, Connie, "Bold Thady Quill", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 38)
    - Side A: Tomelty, Peter, "The Irish Patrol" Side B: Tomelty, Peter, "The Ballad of Jack Kennedy", 1961 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 39)
    - Side A: The Ludlows, "The Winds Thro' The Rafters" Side B: The Ludlows, "That's My Song", 1966 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 40)
    - Side A: The Spinners, "The Orange and the Green" Side B: The Spinners, "Mrs. Houlighan's Christmas Cake", 1965 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 41)
    - Side A: Tomelty, Peter, "Teaching McFadden to Waltz" and "That's How I Spell Ireland" Side B: Tomelty, Peter, "Little Town in the Ould County Down" and "The Inniskilling Dragoons", 1961 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 42)
    - Side A: McBride, Frankie, "Forty Shades of Green" Side B: McBride, Frankie, "How Are Things In Glocca Morra", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 43)
    - Side A: The Johnny Flynn Sound, "Banna Strand" Side B: The Johnny Flynn Sound, "Heart Break Hill", 1970 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 44)
    - Side A: The Moonshiners, "Sean South" Side B: The Moonshiners, "A Mhic Mo Croide", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 45)
    - Side A: Big Tom & The Travellers, "Four Country Roads" Side B: Big Tom & The Travellers, "My Rose of the Mountain", 1981 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 46)
    - Side A: Two's Company, "Eileen McManus" Side B: Two's Company, "Heart's of Stone", 1969 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 47)
    - Side A: Doris, Malachy, "Frost is All Over: Bow-Legged Tailor: Pet of the Pipes", Turkington, Tom, "Kitty's Fancy: Goligher's Frolic" Side B: Turkington, Tom, "Rakes of Kildare: The Cobbler: Humours of Donnybrook" and "Set Dance: Jockey to the Fair", 1962 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 48)
    - Side A: The Gallowglass Ceili Band, "The Rose Waltz" and "The Limerick Waltz" Side B: The Gallowglass Ceili Band, "The Humming Bird Waltz" and "Waltz Selection No. 1 - Rose of Aranmore, Glenswilly, Irish Emigrant", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 49)
    - Side A: The Traditional Irish Musicians Association, "Irish Reels: George White's Favorite, Miss Monaghan, The Copperplate" Side B: The Traditional Irish Musicians Association, "Irish Polkas: Mary Ann, The Dark Girl, Antrim Hills", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 50)
    - Side A: Hegarty, Dermot, "Time To Move Again" Side B: Hegarty, Dermot, "Misty Rolling Midlands", 1969 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 51)
    - Side A: Baxter, John, "Ireland's 32" Side B: Baxter, John, "Boys from the County Cork", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 52)
    - Side A: Real McCoy, "I Get So Excited" Side B: Real McCoy, "Somebody's Taken Maria Away", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 53)
    - Side A: McGuigan, Pat, "Shall my soul pass through Ireland" and "Gwievara Boy" Side B: Dooley, Maisie, "Come down the mountain Katie Daly" and "Come back Paddy Reilly to Bally-James-Duff", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 54)
    - Side A: Owens, Michael, "Saturday Night In Dublin" Side B: Owens, Michael, "Come With Me Molly", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 55)
    - Side A: Wolfe Tones, "The Teddy Bear's Head" and "Deportees (Plane Wreck At Los Gatos)" Side B: Wolfe Tones, "The Jolly Ploughboy" and "I Still Miss Someone", 1967 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 56)
    - Side A: Nellany, Joe, "Peter Street" Side B: Mulvihill, Tommy and Nellany, Joe, "Irish Rebel", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 57)
    - Side A: The Gingerman, "Ha - Penny Bridge" Side B: The Gingerman, "The Alamo", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 58)
    - Side A: The Emeralds, "O Take The News To Washington" Side B: The Emeralds, "Golden Jubilee", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 59)
    - Side A: The Cotorie, "Carnlough Bay" Side B: The Cotorie, "It's Hard To Be Good", 1968 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 60)
    - Side A: Gallagher, Bridie, "Orange Trees Growing In Old County Down" Side B: Gallagher, Bridie, "The Crolly Doll", 1959 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 61)
    - Side A: The Alexander Brothers, "The Flying Scotsmen" Side B: The Alexander Brothers, "Two Little Teardrops", 1967 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 62)
    - Side A: O'Kelly, Betty, "The Green Glens of Antrim" Side B: O'Kelly, Betty, "Connemara Shore", undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 63)
    - Side A: Lynch, Pat, "Treat Me Daughter Kindly" Side B: Lynch, Pat, "Cathedral in the Pines", 1967 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 64)
    - Various, "Music of Ireland" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 65)
    - O'Brien, Paddy and Seamus Connolly, "The Banks of the Shannon" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 66)
    - Moore, Christy, "Ordinary Man" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 67)
    - McGonigle, Mary, "Praise the Lord" and "I Have a Dream" (empty sleeve), 1987 (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 68)
    - Briody, Moira, "Galway Bay" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 69)
    - Wolfe Tones, "Admiral William Brown" (empty sleeve), undated (Box 32, Sound disc--vinyl 70)
    - Side A: McCormack, John, "When Irish Eyes Are Smiling" and "The Kerry Dance" Side B: McCormack, John, "Kathleen Mavourneen" and "Mother Machree", 1916, 1927, 1936 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 1)
    - Side A: Wolfe Tones, "Up And Away (The Helicopter Song)" Side B: Wolfe Tones, "The Broad Black Brimmer", 1973 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 2)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Four Green Fields", Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "When Johnny Comes Marching Home", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 3)
    - Side A: Capitol Showband, "Theme from Lawrence of Arabia" Side B: Capitol Showband, "My Lagan Love", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 4)
    - Side A: Duffy, Thomas, "Roisin Du" Side B: Duffy, Thomas, "An Old Irish Song", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 5)
    - Side A: The Dinkees, "The Ballad of Father Griffin" Side B: The Dinkees, "Deep River", 1968 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 6)
    - Side A: Brady, Sean, "The 'Taoiseachs Hooley'" Side B: Brady, Sean, "Molly Malone", 1983 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 7)
    - Side A: Wolfe Tones, "Flow Liffey Water" and "Flight of Earls" Side B: Wolfe Tones, "Newgrange" and "My Heart Is In Ireland", 1988 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 8)
    - Side A: Wolfe Tones, "Admiral William Brown" Side B: Wolfe Tones, "Cait Ni Dhuibhir", 1982 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 9)
    - Side A: Reilly, Paddy, "The Town I Loved So Well" Side B: Reilly, Paddy, "The Flower of Sweet Strabane", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 10)
    - Side A: Hutchinson, Tony, "When It's Over" Side B: Hutchinson, Tony, "Leave Us And Free Us", 1984 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 11)
    - Side A: Briody, Moira, "Trottin' To The Fair" and "Galway Bay" Side B: Briody, Moira, "A Pretty Irish Girl" and "My Lagan Love", 1963 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 12)
    - Side A: Donohue, Gabriel, "Land Of A Thousand Welcomes" Side B: Donohue, Gabriel, "Only The Rivers Run Free", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 13)
    - Side A: Two's Company, "Eileen McManus" Side B: Two's Company, "Heart's of Stone", 1969 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 14)
    - Side A: Makem, Tommy, and Clancy, Liam, "Maggie Pickens" Side B: Makem, Tommy, and Clancy, Liam, "Bread and Fishes", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 15)
    - Side A: Shine, Brendan, "Three Pubs In Bohola" Side B: Shine, Brendan, "Spuds", 1983 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 16)
    - Side A: Martin Flynn Band, "You Touched Upon My Life" Side B: Martin Flynn Band, "Another Day", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 17)
    - Side A: Moran, Joey, "Flight of Earls" Side B: Moran, Joey, "Pat Murphy's Meadow", 1988 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 18)
    - Side A: The Westmeath Bachelors, "That Tumbledown Shack In Athlone" Side B: The Westmeath Bachelors, "Bonnie Scotland", 1984 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 19)
    - Side A: McCann, Jim, "Love's Old Sweet Song" Side B: McCann, Jim, "Glad I Met You", 1982 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 20)
    - Side A: McGonigle, Mary, "Praise The Lord" Side B: McGonigle, Mary, "I Have A Dream", 1987 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 21)
    - Side A: Moore, Christy, "Ordinary Man" Side B: Moore, Christy, "Another Song Is Born", 1985 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 22)
    - Side A: Columbia Boys, "Baby Come Back" Side B: Columbia Boys, "Born To Lose", 1968 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 23)
    - Side A: Chubby Checker, "Dancin' Party" Side B: Chubby Checker, "Gotta Get Myself Together", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 24)
    - Side A: Quinn, Carmel, "Four Green Fields" Side B: Quinn, Carmel, "When Johnny Comes Marching Home", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 25)
    - Side A: Assoroe Ceili Band, "Morning Clouds", "Dublin Lassies", and "Brown Heifer" Side B: Assoroe Ceili Band, "Blackthorn Stick", "Fr. Kelly's Jig", and "Sweet Biddy Daly", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 26)
    - Side A: Donaghy, Eileen, "Six Mile Song" Side B: Donaghy, Eileen, "Wee Cup Of Tay", 1960 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 27)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry, "In The Misty Moonlight" Side B: Cunningham, Larry, "Fools Paradise", 1967 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 28)
    - Side A: The Go Lucky Four, "Up Went Nelson" Side B: The Go Lucky Four, "The Famine Song", 1966 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 29)
    - Side A: The Millionaires, "The Natural Thing To Do" Side B: The Millionaires, "The Green Leaves Of Summer", 1968 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 30)
    - Side A: Crosbie, Martin, "The Miller's Daughter" Side B: Crosbie, Martin, "I Hate To Lose You", 1967 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 31)
    - Side A: O'Brien, Dermot, "Nora Malone", "Eileen O'Grady", "Siege of Ennis", "The Sword of Columcille", and "The Rose Tree" Side B: O'Brien, Dermot, "The Cuckoo Waltz", "Staten Island", "The Drunken Piper", and "Circassian Circle", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 32)
    - Side A: Makem, Tommy, "Four Green Fields" Side B: Makem, Tommy, "Come By The Hills", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 33)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry, "Pride Of The West" Side B: Cunningham, Larry, "Is Anybody Going to San Antone" and "If You Should Come Back", undated (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 34)
    - Side A: O'Hagan, Patrick, "Queen Of County Clare" Side B: O'Hagan, Patrick, "The Irish Patrol", 1961 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 35)
    - Side A: Gallagher, Bridie, "The Bonny Boy" Side B: Gallagher, Bridie,"A Little Bunch Of Violets", 1967 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 36)
    - Side A: Cunningham, Larry, "Pretty Little Girl From Omagh" Side B: Cunningham, Larry, "The Ballad of James Connolly", 1969 (Box 33, Sound disc--vinyl 37)